Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4272
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- E. COMM. UNIV. INDUS. RELATIONS LIBRNS. E-8 23rd Annual Meeting - McGill Univ. June 6-7, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- E. COMM. UNIV. INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIB. E-8 22nd Annual meeting - Pasadena, Calif. May 31-June 1, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- E. INDUSTRIAL REL. LIBRARIANS COMM. E-11 Feasibility Study, etc., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- E. COMMITTEE UNIV. INDUSTRIAL REL. LIBRNS. E-8 21st Annual Meeting - Princeton May 25-27, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- E INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS COMM. E-8 2oth Annual Meeting May 27-28, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- E INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS COMM. E.8 19th Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- E. INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS' COMM. E-8 Annual Conference May 31-june 1, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  First document slightly crumpled
- E. INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS' COMM. E.8 Annual Conference - Univ. of Calf. 15th, May 26-27, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS COMMITTEE E-8 Annual Conferences - Cleveland June 3-5, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- E. INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS COMM. E-4 Labor Union Publications Index Memorandum, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- E-8 INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS COMM. 13th Annual Conference, June 4-5, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- E. INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS COMM. E-8 12th Annual Meeting, June 1958, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-8 11th Annual Conference May 1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-8 10th Annual Conference 1956 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-5 Correspondence 1955-, 1955-1989 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-5 Correspondence - Subject Headings and Classification, 1949-1962 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-5 Correspondence - Union List, 1948-1960 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-8 9th Annual Conference 1955 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-8 8th Annual Conference 1954 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-8 7th Annual Conference 1953 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-8 6th Annual Conference 1952 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- E. INDUSTRIAL RELATIONS LIBRARIANS COMM. E-8 5th Annual Conference 1951 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-8 4th Annual Conference 1950 2+ 3 also (Box 12, Folder 32)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-10 Mimeographed material, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- E. INDUSTRIAL. RELATIONS. LIBRARIANS. COMM. E-10 Mimeographed material, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 33)